<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <channel>
        <title>Joel Carr Frontend Developer</title>
        <description>Joel Carr is working as a Frontend developer based in London. In this site you can see examples of his work.</description>
        <link>http://joelcarr.github.io/</link>
        <atom:link href="http://joelcarr.github.io/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
        
        <item>
            <title>Sainsbury's Inspiration</title>
            <description>&lt;p&gt;Sainsbury’s wanted a new content-driven site for the countdown to Christmas Day with featured daily homepages showing recipes, articles, and video content. I was responsible for the Wordpress back-end and the responsive front-end.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After Christmas, Sainsbury’s loved the site so much that they have decided to keep it for another two years. Because we had developed our team’s Git workflow, that worked with Jenkins for automated deployments between environments, it was easy to work on multiple versions of the site simultaneously.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 23 Jun 2014 22:10:00 +0100</pubDate>
            <link>http://joelcarr.github.io/project/2014/06/23/sainsburys-inspiration/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">http://joelcarr.github.io/project/2014/06/23/sainsburys-inspiration/</guid>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Barclays Life Skills</title>
            <description>&lt;p&gt;Barclays Life Skills helps teenagers gain vital skills in a variety of areas such as money skills, education, and careers. I was the tech lead for the interactive &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.barclayslifeskills.com/key-skills/getting-to-know-yourself/wheel-of-strengths/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;modules&lt;/a&gt; illustrated and enlivened the lesson. To lighten up the lessons, the modules were highly interactive and visually impressive. I found it particularly fun and rewarding to work with CSS3 animations and Canvas for these modules.&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 22 Jun 2014 13:50:00 +0100</pubDate>
            <link>http://joelcarr.github.io/project/2014/06/22/barclays-life-skills/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">http://joelcarr.github.io/project/2014/06/22/barclays-life-skills/</guid>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Dare website</title>
            <description>&lt;p&gt;The Dare site has been an ongoing project for everyone in my team. Due to our continuous integration approach, we have a backlog of features and bugs. I go through the backlog grouping relevant features and bugs into a new release.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 22 Jun 2014 13:40:00 +0100</pubDate>
            <link>http://joelcarr.github.io/project/2014/06/22/dare-website/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">http://joelcarr.github.io/project/2014/06/22/dare-website/</guid>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>BMW Ultimate Driver</title>
            <description>&lt;p&gt;BMW Ultimate Driver is a Facebook applications that puts users to the test to see if they can assess and react to racing situations. I built the mobile version of the application (built off backbone.js) and also helped concept how it would we could assess the users reactions with limited interaction.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 22 Jun 2014 13:26:00 +0100</pubDate>
            <link>http://joelcarr.github.io/project/2014/06/22/BMW-ultimate-driver/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">http://joelcarr.github.io/project/2014/06/22/BMW-ultimate-driver/</guid>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Post Office Website</title>
            <description>&lt;p&gt;The Post Office new site launch was my first big project at Dare, and the perfect project to kick me off in the agency world. The site was required to meet level Triple-A Conformance to Web Content Accessibility. I worked with a accessibility expert to make sure each component met the require meets of users with impaired vision / hearing / coordination.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 22 Jun 2014 13:22:00 +0100</pubDate>
            <link>http://joelcarr.github.io/project/2014/06/22/post-office-website/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">http://joelcarr.github.io/project/2014/06/22/post-office-website/</guid>
        </item>
        
    </channel>
</rss>
